Cassondra Pascoe

Seattle, Washington
+1 (805) 284-8270
Cassondra.Pascoe@gmail.com

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Birkbeck College, University of London — Master of Science in Organizational Psychology

Coursera — Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate

University of California at Santa Cruz — Bachelor of Arts in Psychology

WORK EXPERIENCE

Johnson Barrow | Seattle, WA

Human Resources Coordinator | Feb 2021 - PRESENT

Facilitate new employee processes by building surveys and presenting found data

Manage HRIS system; assist +130 employees at all levels with benefits enrollment, FMLA, workers compensation, compliance, onboarding, and offboarding

Manage the implementation of new technical equipment and track inventories

Mediterranean Inn | Seattle, WA

Front Office Manager | Feb 2018 - Jan 2020

Lead daily strategies for successful operations, anticipating future hotel needs

Data driven decision-making to maximize revenue; reviewed sales forecasts and strategized across comparable marketplace properties to determine daily rates

Presented revenue data and competitor analysis at quarterly stakeholder meetings

Assistant Front Office Manager | Sept 2016 - Feb 2018

Managed front desk staffing levels; identified areas for additional development

Cultivated key affiliate relationships by identifying and communicating feedback

Compiled training guides and developed metrics to evaluate progress ensuring staff had the resources to provide exemplary service and management support

Front Desk Agent | Sept 2014 - Sept 2016

Created positive guest experiences, anticipating guest needs, and problem solving

Hilton Santa Barbara Beachfront Resort | Santa Barbara, CA Front Office Supervisor | Jan 2014 - Sept 2014 Guest Services Representative | Nov 2012 - Jan 2014

SUMMARY

Proactive entry-level data analytics professional; dedicated to transitioning from a career in Hospitality and Human Resources into data analytics. Experienced in collecting, transforming, and organizing data to help make informed decisions; processing strong communication, problemsolving, collaboration, evidence-based research, and analytical skills.

SKILLS

Proficiency with Excel, SPSS, SQL, Statistics, and Tableau

Learning Python and R

Data Analysis, Data Cleaning, Data Visualization, Effective Data Presentation

PORTFOLIO

Github

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

The Food Bank | Seattle, WA

Dr. Faye Crosby Social Psychology Research | Santa Cruz, CA

Devereux Foundation, Advanced Behavior Health | Goleta, CA